好了 尝一口吧
Okay. Take a sip.
你肯定猜不出饮料里混了什么
You will never guess what's in this one.
脱脂奶  鳄梨汁  花生酱  一丁点青春痘痂
Skim milk, avocado, peanut butter, a hint of zit puss,
芹菜汁和半个嚼烂的鸡块
celery juice and half a chewed-up chicken nugget.
尽管我说过了  但我还是要赞叹一遍
I have said it before, and I will say it again.
太惊人了
Amazing.
小伙子们  小伙子们
Boys boys boys boys boys boys.
准备好欢欣鼓舞吧
Set your phasers to excitement.
好的
Okay.
《太空狼人》的制片人刚刚来电话了
The producers of "space werewolves" just called.
很显然主演的候选名单上还剩下三个人了
There are apparently only three actors still in the running for the lead,
而我就是其中之一
and I'm one of them!
哇
Whoo!
《太空狼人》
"Space werewolves"
是有史以来最伟大的科幻漫画小说了
is the greatest Sci-Fi graphic novel ever.
这是半人半狼的特里斯坦·莱肯和他的
It is the epic tale of Tristan Lycanth, half-wolf, half-human,
星球保卫战的史诗故事
and his battle to save his planet.
就像是《星球大战》和《指环王》的生了个孩子
It is like "star wars" and "lord of t rings" had a baby,
又被了《复仇者联盟》领养长大一样
and then "the avengers" adopted it.
特里斯坦是全宇宙最坏的家伙了
Tristan is the baddest dude in the galaxy.
但是丽芙要出演 编剧就要把角色的性别从男改女
But if Liv gets the part, they're gonna change him to a her.
这样全宇宙最坏的家伙
And then the baddest dude in the galaxy
就成了
will be...
我姐姐
My sister.
伙计们 我最后一次试镜就在这周
Guys, my final audition is in a week.
这个角色也许会让我在电影界一举成名
This is the part that could make me a movie star.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我姐姐就要成为特里斯坦·莱肯了
My sister is gonna be Tristan Lycanth.
和你竞争的那俩倒霉蛋是谁啊
Who are the two losers you're up against?
莱恩·戈斯林和范·迪塞尔
Ryan Gosling and Vin Diesel.
（莱恩·戈斯林 《恋恋笔记本》主演；范·迪塞尔 《拯救大兵瑞恩》主演）
噢
Ohh!
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
b... b... better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
I'm up with the sunshine   let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
I lace up my high tops   oh no
扣篮  热热身
slam dunk   ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
I'm under the spotlight   holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go, go, go
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the other half of me, me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the better half of me, me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
- 嘿  - 嘿  你不是一直说
- Hey. - Hey. You keep saying
想做点亲密的事么
you want to do couple-y things
现在我们都正式喜欢对方了
now that we're officially in like?
呃  其实一直是你在这么说
Well, it's mostly been you that's been saying that,
但是你说话的样子好可爱  继续吧
but you're really cute when you talk, so continue.
那好  我报名参加舞蹈课了
Well, I signed us up for dance lessons.
噢
Ooh.
这挺浪漫的啊
That could be romantic.
哪一种舞  萨尔萨  探戈  华尔兹
What kind? Salsa, tango, waltz?
霹雳舞
Breakdancing!
Breakdancing?
对
Yeah.
呃  迪吉  这一点都不亲密
Um, Diggie, that's not couple-y.
噢  小玛  你大错特错了
Oh, mads, you're so wrong.
我做人浪的时候你刚好能接上
My wave could connect right to your wave.
咋样
What!
啊  做人浪啊
Ah, chain wave.
我也来掺和掺和
Give me some of that.
抱歉了  伙计们  我对霹雳舞很不感冒
Sorry, guys. Breaking's just not really my thing.
真不敢相信我们是同一对父母生的
It's hard to believe we're even related.
呃  嘿  我有个主意
Um, well... hey, here's an idea.
你们俩看起来对霹雳舞这么感兴趣
You guys both seem really excited about this,
为什么不一起上课呢
so why don't you take the lessons together?
然后迪吉嘛 你和我还可以找找有什么我们俩都爱干的事
And then Diggie, you and I can figure out something that we both want to do.
我们现在就是霹雳舞好兄弟了
We are breaking bros now.
做人浪吧
Chain wave.
好  好  做的真不错
Yeah yeah, that was nice.
让你们看看我的动作吧
Now let me show you my wave.
再见了
Buh-bye.
准备好了吗
Ready?
黑面包  桔子酱  花菜浓浆  上等的大腊肠
Rye bread, marmalade, pureed cauliflower, the good bologna
还有一丁点脚趾甲
and just a hint of toenail.
左脚大拇指上的
Left foot, big toe.
完全正确
Nailed it.
小伙子们  你们也知道我对《太空狼人》
Okay. So boys, you got me a little bit nervous
的试镜环节有一点紧张
about my "space werewolves" audition,
所以我决定通过这个来体验狼人生活
so I decided to get my wolf on with this:
艾米·“獠牙”·沃尔夫特撰写的《狼人之道》
"The Way of the Wolf" by Emmy "Fangs" Wulfert.
（艾米·沃尔夫特是本剧主演两个替身的姓名混合体）
“獠牙”是一个青少年的狼人女孩
"Fangs" is a teenage wolf girl.
当她很小的时候  她在一次露营中走散了
When she was little, she wandered off on a camping trip
之后十年就都在丛林中度过  被一群狼养大了
and spent the next 10 years of her life in the wild being raised by wolves.
我还在想玛蒂是不是就这么变成现在这样了
I wonder if that's how Maddie became Maddie.
她喜欢狼  不敢相信
She likes wolves. Big whoop.
我听说范·迪塞尔梦寐以求那个角色  甚至做手术种植了狼的獠牙
I heard diesel wants the part so bad, he had wolf fangs surgically implanted.
什么
What?
而过去整整两个月  戈斯林都在吃公路上被撞死的动物为生
And for the past two months, Gosling's been eating nothing but roadkill.
他们肯定会击败我的
They're gonna crush me.
我需要你们的帮助
Okay, I need your help.
我怎么摸透特里斯坦啊  他最喜欢什么
How do I figure out Tristan? What's his thing?
不用想就知道  当然是他的嚎叫啊
No brainer. It's his howl.
好的  我来试试
Okay, yeah. I got this.
听起来五成像狼  五成像丽芙
It's like 50% wolf, 50% Liv.
你们觉得怎么样啊
What do you guys think?
- 选迪塞尔吧  - 选戈斯林
- Diesel. - Gosling.
哇
Whoa.
刚才的舞蹈太酷了  Q 舞帝
That was awesome, qpop.
对  我从来不会停下脚步
Yeah, q-pop don't stop.
噢
Oh.
J 舞者要驾到了哟
Mc j-town in da house.
J 舞者真有个性
Mc j-town be his own boy.
致敬
Respect!
乔伊  这是 Q 舞帝
Joey, this is q-pop.
他是我们的舞蹈教练
He's our dance instructor.
噢  那好  很高兴见到你  舞帝先生
Oh, well, it's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. pop.
我的使命就是跟随新潮  保持新潮  还要不断刷新潮流
My mission is to get fresh, stay fresh, then refresh.
这就是我的座右铭  托付给你们这犄角旮旯了
I just dropped my motto on this grotto.
这真是酷毙了
This is so cool.
我不敢相信玛蒂不在这儿
I can't believe Maddie bailed.
我简直无拘无束了
I feel so alive.
她失去的正是霹雳舞好哥们得到的
Her loss is the breaking bros' gain.
再说了  谁知道我住在这么一个犄角旮旯呢
Plus, who knew I lived in a grotto.
对吗
Right?
各就各位  让我来看看你们练得咋样了
All right. Let's see what y'all are working with.
来引领潮流吧  呀哈
Time to get fresh, y'all.
当我开始放节奏  我就要看你们跳机器人舞
When I drop the beat, I want to see you robot.
哦  不
Oh... no.
同志们  你们是故意要气哭我吗
Gentlemen, are y'all trying to make q-pop cry?
好了  我们现在退回到几个简单的动作  明白了吗
All right, let's try to back it up to a simpler move, okay?
这个动作叫“找准节奏”
This one is called "finding the beat!"
等一下  慢点来
Okay, wait. Slow down.
你们到底是怎么打响指的啊
How are you making that noise with your fingers?
好了  开始吧
Okay, here we go.
这只不过是个冰棒而已嘛
Okay, this is just frozen mustard.
但是是从哪里进口的
But from where?
是在法国制作的黄色第戎雪糕
A light yellow dijon originally crafted in France
但是加工地在肯塔基州
but now manufactured in Kentucky...
浸泡加工了一次
Dipped once...
不对
no.
是两次
Twice!
浸泡在热狗味的水里
In hot dog water.
啊
Ah.
太激动人心了
Inspiring.
獠牙来了  獠牙来了
Fangs is here! Fangs is here.
噢  是那本书里的女孩么
Ooh, the girl from the book?
对  你们猜准了
Yeah. You guys were right.
我意识到如果我要获得主演资格的话  就必须放手一搏
I've realized that if I want this part I have to do something really big,
所以我聘请了獠牙来引导我演出真正的狼性
so I hired fangs to help me tap into my inner wolf.
丽芙·鲁尼  你的快递
Delivery for Liv Rooney?
- 在这里签收  - 好的
- Sign here. - Okay.
哦
Oh.
这是什么  是不是獠牙把她的行李都提前运过来了
That's so weird. Maybe fangs had all her bags shipped here?
这是獠牙吗
Is that fangs?
不对  哥们  这是另外一个给狼养大的姑娘吧
No, munch, it's a different girl who was raised by wolves.
獠牙你好啊
Hello, fangs!
我是丽芙啊
Me Liv!
我在她的书里学到这招的
I read this in her book.
她必须要熟悉一下陌生人的气味
She has to get used to the smell of new people.
你的气味我能接受
Your scent is acceptable.
抱歉运来了个笼子
Sorry about the cage.
我的狼性太强了  我怕我在陌生人面前控制不住自己
My wolf instincts are strong, and I don't trust myself around new humans.
再说了  把我当货物运更便宜
Plus, it's cheaper to travel in cargo.
那好  獠牙  这是我的弟弟们
Well, fangs, these are my brothers.
不骗你  我还真习惯了
Not gonna lie, I'm into this.
很高兴你的来电  鲁尼
Glad you called, Rooney.
我不会错过任何一个能保证狼
I never miss a chance to make sure wolves
在传媒上大放光彩的机会
are accurately portrayed in the media.
那好吧  如果别人问到了  我就会很骄傲的说
Well, then, if anyone asks, I will proudly state for the record
你没有吃我的奶奶或是把房子炸了什么的
that you did not eat my grandma or blow my house down.
看见了吧  刚才那叫
See, that right there?
无礼攻击
Offensive.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
特里斯坦·莱肯是狼人  半身是狼
Tristan Lycanth is half-wolf.
狼是庄严而又凶猛的生物
Wolves are majestic, fierce creatures.
你身上有这些特性吗  鲁尼
You got any wolf in you, Rooney?
呃  不  她没有
Um, no. No, she does not.
丽芙  她闻过了我的胳肢窝
Liv she sniffed my pits.
我可不敢忽悠她
I can't lie to her.
嚎叫一声听听
Howl for me.
这是成为一只狼最重要的部分
It's the most important part about being a wolf.
这宣示了你的尊严
It asserts your dominance.
我的嚎叫声是有尊严又花哨的
Well, my howl is dom-alicious.
鲁尼  我们的工作量不小啊
Rooney, we have work to do.
什么
What?
你要学会向狼一样生活  捕猎  进食
You're gonna live like a wolf, hunt like a wolf, eat like a wolf
甚至要向狼一样大便
and poop like a wolf.
噢  我可以给她演示最后一种
Oh, I can show her the last one.
没错  我可以模仿 84 种动物大便的方式
Yeah, I can imitate the pooping styles of 84 different animal species.
非常感谢你提供的便便样本  小子
Your offer of a poop demo is appreciated, little man.
但是丽芙现在是我的学生了
But Liv's my student now.
欢迎进入狼的生活
Welcome to my wolf pack.
这简直太酷了
This is gonna be so awesome.
如果你需要上厕所  只要出门直走就可以
And if you need the restroom, it's just back that way.
得了吧
Nah.
在我进来之前就在你们走廊上留了领地标记了
Marked my territory on your porch before I came in.
噢  身上好痒
Ooh, got an itch.
挠不到  挠不到
Can't get it. Can't get it.
- 挠不到  - 好吧
- Can't get it. - Okay.
帮帮同类啊
Help a wolf out!
噢
Oh!
啊  这就舒服多了
Ahh, that's the stuff.
是吗
Yeah?
这狼孩简直疯了
Wolf girl is cray cray.
不过我还需要她训练我身上那种丛林山野的气息
But she is going to give me the forest cred
我才能通过这次试镜
that I need to really nail this audition.
有本事你就把那从马路上拖下来吃了啊  戈斯林
Scrape that off the road and eat it, Gosling.
这些是从把我养大的狼家里带出来的东西
This is from the forest where my wolf family raised me.
这些东西的的味道都不太好闻
Lots of good stink to roll around in.
哦
Oh!
啊
Ah.
舒服啊
Ahh.
到你了  小狼崽子
Your turn, wolf pup.
去打打滚吧
Get up in it.
好吧
Okay.
呼
Whoo.
看看我
Look at me.
在一堆脏兮兮的东西上蹭来蹭去
Scooting around in the filth.
呼
Whoo.
就像是动物一样
Like an animal.
我真是野性十足啊
I am wild!
- 鲁尼  - 怎么了
- Rooney... - Yeah?
- 我就把话直说了吧  - 嗯哼
- Can I get real for a minute? - Mm-hmm?
如果你想在试镜中脱颖而出  你就要像真狼一样
If you want to ace this audition, you have to go full wolf.
狼是领地意识很强的动物
Wolves are territorial animals.
- 好的  - 它们拿走了的东西
- Yeah. - They take what's theirs,
- 就永远别想拿回来了  - 好吧
- and they don't back down. - Yeah.
我们来试试别的吧
Let's try something else.
干嘛呢
What?
你想拿回去么
You want it?
来抢啊
Take it.
好吧
Okay.
我这就去拿水枪
I'm gonna go get the hose.
- 这才叫节奏  - 给力啊
- Sick beat. - Super tight.
看来
So...
你们俩从霹雳舞好哥们发展成
The two of you have gone from breakdancing
耳机都一块用了啊
to sharing ear buds.
真可爱啊
That is so cute.
Q 舞帝说你要敢于分享啊
Q-pop says you gotta dare to share.
对了  说到分享  我最近一直都没看见你了
Yeah. Speaking of sharing, I haven't really seen you much lately.
你想不想放学之后吃点冰激凌呢
Do you want to go grab some fro-yo after school?
哦  求之不得  但是今晚我们要上舞蹈课
Oh, I'd love to, but we have a breaking lesson tonight.
来看看咱们新学的时髦动作
Check out these funky fresh moves.
- 预备 约瑟夫  - 准备好了 小迪
- Ready, Joseph? - So ready, digs.
五  六  七  八
Five, six, seven, eight.
咋样  好啊
What? Yeah!
动一动  哦  哦
Some of this? Oh, oh!
蹲到地板上
And down to the ground.
呃啊
Uh!
拉我起来
Beam me up!
（这句话语出《星际迷航》）
- 咋样  - 酷毙了
- What up? - Fist bump.
亮相吧
Good sesh.
今早的训练太棒了  獠牙
Great training sesh this morning, fangs.
赶鸭子实在是太好玩了
It was so much fun chasing ducks.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
它们真是身在福中不知福
They've had it too good for too long.
我觉得午餐有肉下肚了
I think we've earned lunch.
怎么在地板上吃东西
Eating off the floor.
你们是给狼养大的么
Were you raised by wolves?
妈
Mom.
噢  抱歉抱歉
Oh, sorry sorry.
真是太对不起了
Sorry sorry sorry.
獠牙  你能这么辛苦地训练我真是谢谢了
Thanks for training with me so hard this week, fangs.
我这次试镜胜券在握了
I am going to nail this audition.
我拿定了这个角色  对不对
That part is so mine, am I right?
当一只狼很安静  就说明它不同意我的看法
When the wolf is silent, the wolf disapproves.
到底怎么了
What's wrong?
就你现在的表现而言  唯一能搞定试镜的方式
As good as you're doing, the only way you're gonna nail that audition
就是搞定你的嚎叫声
is if you nail your howl.
这是每一只狼的灵魂所在
It is the heart and soul of any wolf.
呃  我
Wow, I...
觉得你好像吓着所有邻居家的狗狗了
Think you scared every dog in the neighborhood.
不
No.
隔壁街区有只杜宾狗没回复我
There's a doberman on the next block who didn't reply.
这下他回复了
There he is.
他是在道歉
He apologized.
你总不能一边撒尿一边嚎叫吧
You can't pee and bark at the same time.
好了  鲁尼  到你了
Okay, Rooney. Your turn.
好的
Okay.
(曲调是福音歌曲《奇异恩典》)
别再不务正业了
Quit goofing around.
你嚎叫的时候一点都不认真
You're not taking your howl seriously.
跟你说吧
You know what?
我不干了
I'm out.
什么
What?
你不能不干啊  我们是一伙的
You can't be out. We're in a pack.
你还舔过我的脸呢
You licked my face.
抱歉了  鲁尼
I'm sorry, Rooney.
我们已经尽力了
We've gone as far as we can go.
还有就是我总痒痒  但你妈不给我在你们家地毯上挠屁股
Plus, I'm itchy and your mom won't let me drag my butt on your carpet.
你猜怎么着 好吧
You know what? Fine.
我会在没有你的帮助的情况下  成为一个了不起的特里斯坦的
I am going to be an awesome Tristan without your help.
哦  你想吃这块肉么
Oh, you want this?
唔  很好
Mmm. Yeah?
我知道你早就垂涎三尺了
Yeah, I know you want it.
香喷喷的  对不
Yum yum, right?
快去拿吧
Go get it!
真是只笨狼啊
Stupid wolf.
好的  行的  不要  帮我订好  我可不要  橘黄色的  这是谁
Yes, yes, no, book it, hate it, orange... Who is this?!
- 丽芙·鲁尼  大明星啊  - 您好
- Liv Rooney, superstar. - Hi.
我真心想见见这位敢同时叫板
Been dying to meet the girl who's got the nerve
莱恩·戈斯林和范·迪赛尔的女孩
to go up against Ryan Gosling and Vin diesel.
我想看看你今天给我们准备了怎样的视觉盛宴
We are dying to see what you have for us today.
记住  这个角色最重要的特点
Now remember, the most important thing
在于这一段台词最后的仰天长啸
is that big howl at the end of your speech.
放松
Really let loose.
你会有充分的时间准备好
Take all the time you need to get ready.
我不想催你
I don't want to rush you.
开始
And action!
成败在此一举了
This was it.
这是我进军大银幕的机会
This was my chance to become a movie star.
以吾之质子之鞭  降汝于膝下
By the sting of my proton whip, I will bring you to your knees,
以吾为汝之克星
for I am your doom.
吾乃群狼之首
I am wolf.
吾乃特利斯坦·莱肯
I am Tristan Lycanth.
然后和
And?!
对哦  结束
Oh, right. And scene.
我要的狼嚎呢
No, where was my howl?
这没有狼嚎可不行
I need to hear a howl.
从头再来一遍吧
Let's try it again from the top.
好的
Okay.
对了  确认一下  这次不要狼嚎  对吧
Um, just to be clear, though, this is gonna be without the howl?
这次我要你嚎叫出来
With the howl.
对哦
Right.
你们两个小棉花糖一踏上跳舞毯
When you two marshmallows first stepped up to the mat,
我就知道霹雳舞就是你们的需要的火
I was like "breakdancing is gonna roast them alive."
我也尽了严师的责任了
But I've been spitting a little knowledge to you two,
而你们也算是朽木可雕
and you all have soaked it up.
舞王玛蒂来了
Mix master Maddie in the house!
哦
Joey: Yeah.
玛蒂  你来干嘛
Maddie, what are you doing here?
迪吉  我意识到
Diggie, I realized that...
所谓情侣
Being a part of a couple
有时就需要爱屋及乌
means sometimes doing things that the other person likes.
所以  我和 Q 舞帝会过  他教了我一些舞步
So I met up with q-pop earlier, and he taught me a couple moves.
我觉着吧  不成功便成仁
I figure if I can't beat 'em, break 'em.
成仁不成那就来跳舞吧
Oh, and if you can't break 'em, breakdance.
说真的  玛蒂  霹雳舞可是 J 舞者和 D 大哥的菜  喔
Seriously, Maddie, breakdancing is mc j-town and dig-dog's thing... whoa!
来吧  Q 舞帝
Cue it, pop.
喔  就是这样
Oh, that's how I do!
就是这样
And that is how I do.
哇  好吧  乔伊  走起
Yeah, okay. Beat it, Joey.
我是说那个走起
The other "beat it."
知道啦
I know.
好
Okay.
准备来一个狼人的嚎叫吧  很关键哦
Get ready for a howl that is going to change your life.
好咧  准备好了
(Chuckles) Okay, get ready.
来了哦
It's coming. (Clears throat)
你知道的
Although, you know...
刚刚想了想
Just sort of like off the top of my head,
少点吼叫多点清脆怎么样
what if it was sort of less of a howl and more of a whistle?
嗯  嗯
Yeah, yeah.
我是说  观众完全
'Cause I mean, the audience totally...
你嚎一嗓子不就是了吗
just howl!
明白
Got it.
我叫“獠牙”·沃尔夫特  我是来这儿试镜特里斯坦的
My name is Fangs Wolfert, and I'm here to try out for the part of Tristan.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
给我一分钟时间和我的狼人教练私聊一会儿
Just give me one second to talk to my wolf coach real quick.
给我出去
Get out.
狼人  有志者事竟成
A wolf takes what it wants.
我现在就要拿下这个角色
And I'm taking this part.
噢
Oh.
我们可是在舞台上  獠牙
We are on a soundstage right now, fangs.
这是我的地盘
This is my territory.
此言差矣
Doesn't look like it.
我是特里斯坦·莱肯
I am Tristan Lycanth.
不  我才是特里斯坦·莱肯
No, I am Tristan Lycanth.
结束
And scene.
哇哦
Wow.
我们讨论一下然后回来
Let us discuss and we'll get back to you.
你们去搞清楚是谁帮这个棕发妹子做的头发
Find out who styles the brunette's hair.
简直是超爱
I love it.
獠牙
Fangs!
这一出我早都安排好了
All part of my plan.
哦哦
Oh-ho...
你还真不赖
You are good.
我知道只要我挑战你的地盘  咱们所有的努力都会有回报的
I knew that if I threatened your territory, all our hard work would pay off
而你的狼人本性就会显露无疑
and your inner wolf would emerge.
虽然不知道我有没有胜过戈斯林和迪赛尔
Well, I don't know if I'd beat Gosling or diesel,
但是  我做到了獠牙  我吼出来了
but I did it, fangs. I howled.
是的
I heard.
你听起来简直就像我妈
It sounded like my mother.
噢  我要紧张死了
Oh, this tension is killing me.
咱们的宝贝女儿可能就要进军大银幕了
Our little baby could be a movie star.
不是可能  是一定
Not could be. Will be.
大家注意
Guys guys guys guys.
她到了
She just pulled up.
全体人员  正常正常
Okay, everybody just act normal.
好的好的
Okay...
敢不敢更正常一点
More normal than that.
大家好
Hey guys.
哦  不
Oh no.
说回来  谁能比戈斯林和迪塞尔更出色呢
Oh well, who can beat Gosling and Diesel?
就是
Yeah.
丽芙·鲁尼  就是我啊
Liv Rooney, that's who!
我拿到角色了
I got the part!
我要演特里斯坦·莱肯啦
I'm gonna be Tristan Lycanth.
太棒了
This is amazing news!
绝对要庆祝一下
Let's celebrate!
狂欢一下
We need to party!
- 喔喔喔  - 狂欢
- Whoop whoop whoop! - Party!
- 我想  - 狂欢
- I want to... - Party.
- 我想  - 大伙  大伙
- I need to... - Guys, guys?
我真的真的真的很想
I really really really appreciate that,
但是试镜真的让我精疲力尽了都
but I'm pretty wiped out from the audition,
所以我还是去睡一觉比较好
so I think I'm just gonna go to bed.
晚安
Good night.
六  七  八
Six, seven, eight.
- 动起来  - 喔喔喔
- Party! - Whoop whoop whoop!